<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events flow on ODA Documentation Site</title>
    <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/guides/eventsflow/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events flow on ODA Documentation Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/guides/eventsflow/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Events processing</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/guides/eventsflow/eventsprocessing/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/guides/eventsflow/eventsprocessing/index.html</guid>
      <description>In StateManager- InMemory bundle, when a new event from a device arrives, it is processed executing a number of steps:
Rules associated to the datastreamId of the event are applied to the event. There can be N rules to be applied.
Once all rules have been applied, we retrieve from StateManager memory all the datastreamIds which have been marked as &amp;lsquo;refreshed&amp;rsquo; (there is a new value for that datastreamId) or as &amp;lsquo;sendImmediately&amp;rsquo;.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Events collection</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/guides/eventsflow/eventscollection/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/guides/eventsflow/eventscollection/index.html</guid>
      <description>In Collector bundle, when we have to collect events stored in StateManager memory a number of steps is executed:
Get from memory all events whose datastreamId and deviceId are equals to the ones that triggered the process (all those configured in the collector config file for this moment).
Get from database all existing values for the datastreamId and deviceId indicated.
Using the values obtained from the database, all values stored in memory are updated.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Events erasure</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/guides/eventsflow/eventserasure/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/guides/eventsflow/eventserasure/index.html</guid>
      <description>In StateManager-InMemory bundle, events are stored in memory and in the database. We need a process that erases old events that are no longer needed to avoid using too much disk and memory. This process is done in different places and bundles.
There are three parameters in StateManager configuration file that are used in these process:
maxData - indicates how many values can be stored for any datastreamId, deviceId combination.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>