<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Connectors on ODA Documentation Site</title>
    <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Connectors on ODA Documentation Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>COAP</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/coap/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/coap/index.html</guid>
      <description>This connector enables communication via CoAP Protocol.
Only allows to send data to the OpenGate platform. Operations can&amp;rsquo;t be received.
Dependencies This module requires the following modules:
Core Commons: Provides many interfaces that this module will use. Device Info Provider: Needed to know the Device Id of the device that are running the Agent, and the API Key to access to OpenGate. Both data are required to achieve a connection with OpenGate and transferred data will have the deviceId in its metadata.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>DNP3</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/dnp3/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/dnp3/index.html</guid>
      <description>This connector enables communication via DNP3 Protocol.
Allow the transfer of data and operations with an SCADA third-system that implements an DNP3 master (client).
Dependencies This module requires the following modules:
Scada Table Info: Needed to serve to the connector the information of inputs, outputs and counters and can create a DB with them. Scada Dispatcher: Needed to process the payloads and de/serialize its content. Core Commons: Provides many interfaces that this module will use.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>HTTP</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/http/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/http/index.html</guid>
      <description>HTTP This connector enable communication via HTTP Protocol.
Only allows to send data to the OpenGate platform. Operations can&amp;rsquo;t be received.
Dependencies This module requires the following modules:
Core Commons: Provides many interfaces that this module will use. Device Info Provider: Needed to know the Device Id of the device that are running the Agent and the API Key to access to OpenGate. Both data are required to achieve a connection with OpenGate and transferred data will have the deviceId in its metadata.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>IEC 104</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/iec104/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/iec104/index.html</guid>
      <description>IEC 104 This connector enable communication via IEC 104 Protocol.
Allow the transfer of data and operations with a SCADA third-system that implements an IEC 104 master (client).
Dependencies This module requires the following modules:
Core Commons: Provides many interfaces that this module will use. IEC104 Communications Module: Needed to create the IEC104 client that will connect to the third system. Scada Dispatcher: Needed to process the payloads and de/serialize its content.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>MQTT</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/mqtt/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/mqtt/index.html</guid>
      <description>MQTT This connector enable communication via MQTT Protocol.
Allows to send data to the OpenGate platform and receive operations from it.
Dependencies This module requires the following modules:
Core commons: Provides many interfaces that this module will use Mqtt Communications Module: Needed to create the MQTT client that will connects to the MQTT broker of the third system. Dispatcher: Needed to process the payloads and de/serialize its content. Device Info Provider: Needed to know the Device Id of the device that are running the Agent, and the API Key to access to OpenGate.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WebSocket</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/websocket/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/layers/connectors/websocket/index.html</guid>
      <description>WebSocket This connector enable communication via WebSocket Protocol.
Allows to send data to the OpenGate platform and receive operations from it.
Dependencies This module requires the following modules:
Core commons: Provides many interfaces that this module will use Device Info Provider: Needed to know the Device Id of the device that are running the Agent and the API Key to access to OpenGate. Both data are required to achieve a connection with OpenGate and transferred data will have the deviceId in its metadata.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>