<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scenarios on ODA Documentation Site</title>
    <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/index.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scenarios on ODA Documentation Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>New Software</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/updatesoftware/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/updatesoftware/index.html</guid>
      <description>ODA has an update operation that allows to install or update software, rules or configuration in ODA from a third system.
We must configure the parameters needed for this operation in file es.amplia.oda.operation.update.cfg. It will take five parameters:
rulesPath - path of the folder where rules will be installed (rules/)
rulesUtilsPath - path of the folder where auxiliary javascript files to use with rules will be installed (jslib/)
backupPath - path of the folder where backups will be made (backup/)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Recollect Data</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/recollectdata/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/recollectdata/index.html</guid>
      <description>Request data periodically from devices Using ODA capabilities we can request data periodically from a device using one of the interfaces defined in ODA.
Configure the hardware connection to the device. This is done in the corresponding configuration file of that hardware interface es.amplia.oda.hardware.*.cfg. To know the parameters needed to configure the hardware interface we want to use, check the Layers/Hardware section in this guide.
Configure the datastream that will contain the data retrieved by the hardware layer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Publish Data</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/publishdata/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/publishdata/index.html</guid>
      <description>Publish data recollected from devices Once we have recollected data from the device, we must publish that data to OpenGate or another external system. There are two modes in which ODA can work to publish data:
Real time - datastreams are published as soon as they are recollected from the poller
In memory - datastreams are stored in a database awaiting to be published
In real time mode, there is no configuration to be done.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Apply Rules</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/applyrules/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/applyrules/index.html</guid>
      <description>Apply rules to the collected data ODA allows to configure custom rules to be applied after the data is collected from the device. Rules are only applied if we are using in memory state manager.
Rules are javascript files composed of two methods:
when - this method defines the conditions that must be met for the rule to apply. Returns boolean indicating if the result is true or false. then - this method defines the changes we want to apply to the datastream.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Read data from IEC104 devices</title>
      <link>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/readdataiec104/index.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://amplia-iiot.github.io/oda-docs/scenarios/readdataiec104/index.html</guid>
      <description>Read data from an IEC104 device ODA allows to read data from an IEC104 device using these bundles:
es.amplia.oda.datastreams.iec104 es.amplia.oda.comms.iec104 es.amplia.oda.service.scadatables We will explain how to configure these bundles to connect to the device and to read data from it.
The first step is to configure the connection with the device. This is defined in the configuration of datastreams bundle (es.amplia.oda.datastreams.iec104.cfg):
pollingTime=10000 iec104DeviceId=127.0.0.1;2404;1 The pollingTime parameter indicates the seconds between executions of Interrogation Commands.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>